how can i pay off my manulife one
account more quickly
most of us dream of the day we become
debt-free
we think of it as a time of reduced
stress freedom to travel
or even an important step towards
retirement
we want to help you get there sooner
you've taken a great first step by
switching to manulife one
now take these three steps used by our
most successful
manulife one customers one have your
income automatically deposited into your
manulife one account
every time you get paid your debt goes
down and you'll pay less interest
two use the money from your other
checking and savings accounts to pay
down your manulife one balance
remember you pay more interest on your
debt than you earn on your savings
three spend less than you earn this
is key keeping your extra money in your
account
reduces your debt and the amount of
interest you pay
want to find some extra money in your
budget review your expenses
and see if there's somewhere you can cut
back take these three simple steps
and you'll be on your way to becoming
debt free
you